

□ (+86) 186-0068-0592 | **y**tjia.zju@gmail.com | **n** ytjia

Summary

Current Machine Learning Engineer in Bitu. 4+ years experience specializing in Machine Learning applications and Large-scale Data processing. Interested in designing and building Machine Learning applications to solve real-world problems, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience

Bitu Beijing, China

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

Mar. 2018 - PRESENT

Building and optimizing recommender system

Didi ChuxingBeijing, China

SENIOR ALGORITHM ENGINEER

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2018

- Worked on SDP(Supply-Demand Prediction) project. Designed and built demand regression and supply-demand gap classification predictive
 model. Mined business features and implemented different state-of-art models to optimize model performance. Built and maintained SDP
 service used for Dispatching and Intelligent Marketing.
- Worked on Intelligent Marketing project. Designed and built user-activation, user-loss and bubble-order(like CTR) predictive model used for
 user targeting in Intelligent Marketing.

Meituan Beijing, China

DATA MINING ENGINEER

Jul. 2014 - Feb. 2016

- Worked on hotel ranking system. Implemented and maintained microservice of ranking system used for large-scale, real-time, personalized hotel searching. Designed and built machine learning pipeline for CTR and CVR model. Mined business features and implemented different state-of-art models to optimize CTR prediction. Resulted in paying rate increasing from 6% to 14%.
- Worked on channel traffic monitoring system. Built ETL pipeline to collect critical user actions like impression, click, order and refund and calculate according conversion rates at different stages. Presented important statistic results with dashboards and automated reports.
- Gain S score(<3%) twice in performance evaluations.

Meituan Beijing, China

• Worked on hotel customer profile mining. Used stats and machine-learning to find user order patterns in data.

• Worked on cheating device detection.

Microsoft Beijing, China

SOFTWARE DEVELOP ENGINEER INTERN

May. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Nov. 2013 - Apr. 2014

- Participated in developing Bugsearcher(an internal tool) and it's monitoring service.
- Transplanted Ford's open source product AppLink from POSIX to Windows.

Education

ZJU(Zhejiang University)

Hangzhou, China

M.S. IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2014

ZJU(Zhejiang University)

Hangzhou, China

B.S. IN ELECTRONIC AND INFORMATION ENGINEERING

Aug. 2008 - Jul. 2012

- Excellent Social Work Scholarship
- · Outstanding Student Leader Award

Skills

Programming Python, Java, Scala, C, Bash

Distributed Computing Spark, Hive, Hadoop

Machine Learning scikit-learn, TensorFlow; LR, GBDT, LSTM and so on.

Dev Tool MacOS/Linux + IDEA/Vim + Git

Product Time Series Prediction, Intelligent Marketing, Learning to rank

Languages Chinese, English,